□ (+1) 202-569-0417 | Image: Image:

Summary_

Graduate Student in Computer Science & Applications at Virginia Tech. Expert in Deep Learning, focused on generating synthetic data-sets, loves working on distributed systems. 5+ Years of experience in the industry, specialized in development of Micro-Services on Kubernetes, System Administration, Object Storage, DNS and CDN Systems. Loves Linux and Mac, vs code and neovim user. Prefers to use Golang and Python, expert in nginx, PostgreSQL and Redis. Uses Docker & Kubernetes for everything.

Education

Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University

Jan. 2019 - Present

Blacksburg, VA, US

M.Sc. in Computer Science & Applications **University of Tehran**

B.Sc. in Computer Engineering Sep. 2011 - Aug. 2016

Work Experience_____

Café Bazaar

Jul. 2015 - Dec. 2018 SOFTWARE ENGINEER

- Developed a Distributed Object Storage using Redhat Ceph for Café Bazaar Cloud
- Developed a Reverse Proxy that integrated Café Bazaar's IAM with Rados Gateway
- Developed a CDN Service on Café Bazaar Cloud CDN Systems and its Operator service on Kubernetes
- Developed a Distributed Global Server Load Balancer for Café Bazaar Cloud
- Developed CDN Purge and Video Conversion API Services on Kubernetes
- · Migrated Café Bazaar Developers Panel from docker-compose to Kubernetes with fully integrated CI/CD Pipelines in GitLab

Café Bazaar

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER Aug. 2013 - Jun. 2015

- Designed and Developed "5ShanbeBazaar", a website dedicated to an event focused on mobile application developers with scheduling and ticket management
- Co-Designed and Developed Café Bazaar's Developers Panel
- Redesigned Café Bazaar's Website

Technical Skills_

THEORETICAL BACKGROUND

· Experienced in Deep Learning, Design of Algorithms, Data Structures, Database Design, Networking and GPGPU

PROGRAMMING AND SCRIPTING

- Expert in Golang, C/C++, Java and Python
- Experienced Lua, BashScript, JavaScript, Node.js, Matlab/Octave, VHDL and Verilog
- · Familiar with PHP and Rust

DEEP LEARNING FRAMEWORKS

· Experienced in PyTorch, Keras and TensorFlow

TECHNOLOGIES

- · Expert in Docker, Kubernetes, nginx, Django, Redis and PostgreSQL
- Experienced in WebSocket, NodeJS, VueJS, ReactJS, Sass and Apache Kafka
- · Familiar with neo4j and MongoDB
- I Use Git, Vim, VS Code, Docker, ZSH, ,Make and धा=X on a daily basis

- Expert in Linux and MacOS
- Experienced System Administrator of more than 60 DNS and CDN servers

LANGUAGE

- · Persian: Native
- English: Fluent (TOEFL iBT score: 113)

Mohi Beyki · Résumé OCTOBER 12, 2019

Research Experience

Digital Library Research Lab @ Virginia Tech

Blacksburg, VA, US

RESEARCH ASSISTANT Aug. 2019 - Present

• I'm focused on generating synthetic healthcare records (EHR) using Generative Adversarial Networks while preserving privacy. I work with Dr. Fox and Ph.D. candidate Amirsina Torfi

Institute for Research in Fundamental Sciences (IPM)

Tehran, Irar

May. 2017 - Feb. 2017

Feb. 2015 - Nov. 2015

RESEARCHER

Developed an automatic parallelization tool that took advantage of GPUs and CPUs of the host machine
 Worked on temperature aware modeling and evaluation of real time embedded multiprocessor SoCs

University of Tehran Tehran, Ira

· Developed a distributed matrix multiplication platform using Golang and OpenCL on a GPU cluster (B.Sc. Thesis Project)

Interests_

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Software Engineering
Deep Learning & Machine Learning
Distributed Systems
High Performance Computing

Honors & Awards.

- 2016 Ranked 29th (among 10,000 participants) National M.Sc. Entrance Examination in Hardware Engineering
- 2015 **Outstanding School Service** ACM Student Chapter Excellence Award
- 2013 Ranked Top 30 ACM ICPC Regional Contest
- 2011 Ranked 243rd (among 300,000 participants) National University Entrance Examination in Math and Physics

Teaching Experience _____

2019	Software Design & Data Structures Teaching Assistant of Prof. Ellis	Virginia Tech
2019	Cloud Software Development Teaching Assistant of Dr. Back	Virginia Tech
2016	Kubernetes Workshop Café Bazaar	UT
2015	Computer Networks Teaching Assistant of Dr. Khonsari	UT
2014	Internet Engineering Teaching Assistant of Dr. Shafiee	UT
2014	Data Structures in Java ACM Student Chapter	UT
2013	Introduction to Computers & Programming Teaching Assistant of Dr. Moradi	UT
2013	Web Development with RoR & JavaScript ACM Student Chapter	UT

Leadership and Membership

- 2015 Author ACM Student Chapter Scientific Journal F1
- 2014 Webmaster ACM Student Chapter